

PUSHP RAJ

PROFILE

Here is a Tech - Marketing enthusiast pursuing B.Tech focused in Electronics and Communication Engineering from Manipal University. I am proficient at coding in Java as well as Python and I am learning about Microsoft Azure Cloud Services lately.

In addition to that, I have got hands-on experience in Full-Stack Web Development, having developed several projects using Django and I've been into Product Marketing with Managerial Experience for quite some time.

SKILLS SUMMARY

Coding Languages

Python, Java, JavaScript, SQLite, C++, HTML, CSS

Frameworks

Django, Bootstrap, Visual Studio Code, ReactJS

Operating Systems macOS, Linux

Graphic Designing

Adobe Illustrator, Adobe Premiere Pro

INTERESTS

WEB DEVELOPMENT
MARKETING
FINANCIAL MANAGEMENT
LEADERSHIP
BUSINESS DEVELOPMENT
GRAPHIC DESIGN

HOW TO REACH ME

Phone: +91 8750905359 Email: rajpushp64egmail.com

LinkedIn: www.linkedin.com/in/rajpushp12

WORK EXPERIENCE

MARKETING MANAGER - Product OGV AND OGTa

AIESEC IN M.A.H.E. | JAN 2021 to Present

- Leading the Content Creation and PR Team.
- Building University Relations around M.A.H.E.
- The team generated the highest Sign-Ups in India.

CONTENT CREATOR - NATIONAL SUPPORT TEAM

AIESEC IN HUNGARY | AUG 2020 to JAN 2021

- Created Product Based Contents at the Member Committee.
- Helped the team in updating the front-end and UI of their site.

PROJECTS

Instruction: Tap on the names to open the source code.

DecentraSpot

This is an exchange site for Decentralised Currencies, where people can trade and earn profits.

Commerce

E-Commerce auction site that allows users to post the auction listings and place bids on them.

EDUCATIONAL TRAINING

THE INDIAN PUBLIC SCHOOL, DEHRADUN

2010 - 2018 | CISCE 2016 | CBSE 2018

- 92.00% in ICSE Class 10th.
- 91.20% in CBSE Class 12th.
- School Editorial Board Member.
- Gold medalist in Bussiness Quiz at Doon Business School.
- Represented Uttarakhand in 3 National Cricket Tournaments.

MANIPAL INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY, MANIPAL

2019 - 2023 | B.Tech - Electronics and Communication

- CGPA 8.98
- Member Youth for Volunteering
- Athlete Manipal Runners Club
- Marketing Team Lead AIESEC in M.A.H.E.